<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FragmentmodularDesignDemo</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>


    <string-array name="titles">

        <item>Activities</item>
        <item>Services</item>
        <item>Content Providers</item>
        <item>Processes and Thread</item>
        <item>Permissions</item>


    </string-array>

    <string-array name="discriptions">
        <item>An Activity is an application component that provides a screen with which users can interact in order to do something, such as dial the phone, take a photo, send an email, or view a map. Each activity is given a window in which to draw its user interface. The window typically fills the screen, but may be smaller than the screen and float on top of other windows.</item>
        <item>A Service is an application component that can perform long-running operations in the background and does not provide a user interface. Another application component can start a service and it will continue to run in the background even if the user switches to another application. Additionally, a component can bind to a service to interact with it and even perform interprocess communication (IPC). For example, a service might handle network transactions, play music, perform file I/O, or interact with a content provider, all from the background.</item>
        <item>Content providers manage access to a structured set of data. They encapsulate the data, and provide mechanisms for defining data security. Content providers are the standard interface that connects data in one process with code running in another process.</item>
        <item>When an application component starts and the application does not have any other components running, the Android system starts a new Linux process for the application with a single thread of execution</item>
        <item>Declares a security permission that can be used to limit access to specific components or features of this or other applications. See the Permissions section in the introduction, and the Security and Permissions document for more information on how permissions work.</item>


    </string-array>

</resources>
